Guide to the School of Business and Public Management records, 1925-2004 RG0013
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
School of Business and Public Management records
1925-2013
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
RG0013
61 Linear Feet
Collection contains correspondence, reports, student records, course materials, and publications. The material dates from 1925 to 2004. These records relate to the work of the departments included in the School of Business and Public Management and records from the Office of the Dean.
Restrictions on Access
Series 9 is closed to research for 25 years from date of record creation. Student records in Series 8 and 9 are closed for 100 years from date of record creation. Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from the School of Business and Public Management.
Historical Note
The George Washington University's School of Business offers renowned programs in international business, finance, and entrepreneurship/small business, and the school prides itself on offering students flexibility in their programs of study. In 2004, the Board of Trustees renamed the School of Business and Public Management the School of Business, and reorganized the Public Administration Department into the School of Public Policy and Public Administration (within the Columbian College of Arts and Sciences).
The George Washington University has offered government and business-type course for nearly a century, but the institutional entity now known as the School of Business had its modern origins in 1928 when University President Cloyd Heck Marvin accepted a million-dollar endowment from the League of Masonic Clubs to establish what was then known simply as the School of Government.
Since its founding in 1928 the School has benefited notably, and perhaps uniquely, from the continuing generosity of Masonic groups. Their funding of the Scottish Rites Fellowships and Wolcott Scholarships assured the recruiting of top-ranked students, and what might be called the School Masonic connection continued when Stephen Joel Trachtenberg, a Mason, became President of the University.
The grouping of business, government, and international affairs remained intact until 1966 when President Lloyd H. Elliott split their faculties into separate schools: one, the School of Public and International Affairs, which later became the Elliott School of International Affairs, the other, the School of Government and Business Administration renamed in 1990 as the school of Business and Public Management.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains correspondence, reports, student records, course materials, and publications. The material dates from 1925 to 2004. These records relate to the work of the departments included in the School of Business and Public Management and records from the Office of the Dean.
PLEASE NOTE: This collection does not have a series #19
Collection Organization
Organized into nineteen series: four series of Departmental files, and one series of History files, Health Care Administration Department, Office of the Dean, Office of the Dean, Research and continuing professional education, Public Administration Department, Departmental files, Finance Department, Duques building, Videotapes, Publications, "Policy Perspectives," "Washington Edition," "Tuesday Report," Business Administration Department, Ben Burdetsky files.
Collection note
Please note: there is no series 19.
Reports and studies; Seminars; Conferences; Washington (D.C.); Courses and lectures; George Washington University; George Washington University. School of Business; George Washington University--Alumni and alumnae
- History files, 1988; RG0013 Series 1; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains a history of school of government and business administration by H. R. Page. This material is dated 1988.
- Health Care Administration Department, 1972; RG0013 Series 2; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains survey questionnaires. These items have a date of 1972. These questionnaires are for graduate programs in hospital administration and paper health planning topics for the HCA course 212.
- Office of the Dean, 1983-1992; RG0013 Series 3; 12 Linear feet
  This series contains minutes, and correspondence. The material dates from 1983-92 and covers various subjects including personnel files, council of deans, alumni association, and correspondence of Ben Burdensky.
  - Shepherd, Charles, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Shouldice, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Witmer, Phillip, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Snelgrove, Scott, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sommers, Waldo, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meany, Judith, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stevens, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Zak, Lev, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Frost, Brian, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Greaney, Catherine, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ibrahim, Hassan, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ott, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Divvens, Deanna, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - West, Diana, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Co-op Advisory Board, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Council of Deans: Agenda/Minutes, 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - SBPM Annual Report, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee: Agenda/Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Associates Council: Agenda/Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Accountancy, 1985-1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Finance:, 1985-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Annual Reports:, 1985-1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Grants/ Awards:, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Academic Dishonesty, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Finance Department, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - BAD finance, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Anderson, Roblyn, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bennett, Elaine, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bossard, Kenneth, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Capers, Gregory Keith, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Clark, Janine, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Coopman, Mary C., undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Daniell, Abby S., undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Empfield, William, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Finaish, Rushrsa, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Fullenwilder, Sharon Y., undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Hammond-Walker, Arnell, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Hodges, Virginia, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Heffron, Dianne, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Hudson-Garber, Eugenia, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Kelley, Paula, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Lewis, Mark, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Liu, Yaqing, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Luick, Katherine, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - MacNamara, Mary B., undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Moody, Stella, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Paxton, Jerry, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Randolph, Toni, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Rueda, Gabriela, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Stellars, Catherine A., undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Tonson, Catherine, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Voskyylen, Margaret, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Ware, Athena, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Yarusso, Amanda, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Soviets/Russia/LeVak, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Executive Program (SEP), undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Japan, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - NOVA, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - MBA/MPA/EPA, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Aspesi, Peter, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Baker, doris, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Betts, Cheryl, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Donberger, Mark, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Dooley, Yvonne, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Manuszak, Nancy, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - McCaskill, Horace, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - McKee, Michael, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Urban and Regional Planning, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Service Master Award, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Study Abroad, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Becker, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Birnbaum, Philip, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bryant, Sarah, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Crum, Gary, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Greene, Sherwin, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Hardgrave, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Kurtz, Frederick, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Lin, Chan-Jane, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Loeser, Norma, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Longstreth, Richard, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Lovell, Malcolm, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Reeves, Philip, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Segal, Frank, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Public Policy Research Institute, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - SBPM Misc., 1991 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - SBPM Misc., 1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Health Policy Research Proposal, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Guidelines for Research Center, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Hours: Flextime, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Distinguished Research Professorships, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Recruitment, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Fculty Senate, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Law Suits: Purcell, Thrinnanzi vs. Greene, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Association, 1985-1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Enrollment:, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Student Grievance Review Committee:, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Development/ Alumni Relations, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Association - Functions/Awards:, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Development/ Prospective donors:, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - AACSB/ Accreditation:, 1977-1991 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Report on Middle States Association:, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Accountancy Department:, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - DC Private Industry Council:, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - World Economic Development Conference:, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - CEO of the Year, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Middle States Accreditation:, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Middle States Accreditation:, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - AACSB:, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - AACSB:, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - AACSB:, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Accountancy Department, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Deans Correspondence Files Burdensky, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - SBPM Curriculum Programs, 1986-1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - SBPM Placement File, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - SGBA Curriculum Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - NOVA, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Humor Project, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - IBUS Curriculum and Correspondence:, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Performance Evaluations/Grievances Stephen Drapeau, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Total Quality Management (TQM), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Len Zak, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - International Exchange: Academic Co-op, 1978-1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Japan, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Hungary, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Franklin College, Switzerland, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Non-Faculty Review, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Office of the Dean, 1953-1962; RG0013 Series 4; 0.5 Linear feet
  This series contains office files. These materials date from 1953-62 and relate to the subjects of defense advertising cost policy and the essential records for individuals and re-establishment of individual rights.
  - Defense Advertising Cost Policy, 10/1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Essential Records for Individual Identification and Re-establishment of Individual Rights, 07/1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Research and continuing professional education, 1981-1992; RG0013 Series 5; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series contains writings and conference proceedings reports. This material dates from 1981-92.
  - Impact on Water Resources of Cattle Production Shifts in the Southwestern and Southeastern United States, 03/1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academy of International Business: United States Southeast Regional Meeting Proceedings, 11/1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The New American Workplace: Shaping the Public Policy Debate, 12/1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings of the GW University Seminar on Neural Networks (EE 217), 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Codetermination in the United States: Union Involvement in Strategic Corporate Decision Making, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Computer Literacy and the Business School: A Time For Change?, 07/1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - School of Government and Business Administration, a History and Memoir, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Business Unit, Vol. 2: Faculty Data Sheets, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Working Papers in Business Administration, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Proceedings: Washington Consortium Schools of Business first Annual Forum, 04/1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Why We Don't Teach Ethics in B School, 02/1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Effective Communication: The Key to Multi-Cultural Exchange, 01/1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Tenth Annual Conference on Teaching Public Administration, 04/1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - A Presentation on Professional Accreditation: The American Assembly of Collegiate Schools of Business, 09/1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Writings by S.J. Rosenberg, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Departmental files, 1988; RG0013 Series 6; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series contains documents from 1988 that relate to the search for a new dean.
  - Dean Search, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abert, James G., undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bohen, Frederick M., undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Seale, William, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Boer, Germain, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Nominations, 03/21/1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Trumble, Robert R., undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Weiss, Ira R., undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Nominations, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Deans, Robert H., undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Follain, James R., undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Wu, Frederick H., undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Sheehan, Jeffrey A., undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ziegler, Ronald L., undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Aaron, Henry, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Ahearne, John F., undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bohen, Frederick M., undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Dawkins, Peter, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Fiedler, Edgar R., undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ford, William F., undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Gramm, Wendy Lee, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Heggestad, Arnold, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Kingon, Alfred H., undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Miller, James C., III, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - O’Toole, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Tisano, Jane G., undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Plager, S. Jay, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Polhman, Randolph Allen, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Prince, Gregory Smith, Jr., undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Reich, Robert B., undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Rist, Ray L., undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Williams, Gary G., undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Sonnenfeld, Jeffrey A., undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Young, Frank E., undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Lantz, Keith W., undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Lee, Ronald S., undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Leister, Douglas V., undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Lewin, Arie Y., undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - McLean, Kenneth A., undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Morris, Archie, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Mulligan, Peter M., undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Patten, Ronald J., undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Prestowitz, Clyde, Jr., undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Price, Harvey s., undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Richardson, Richard W., undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Richburg, Max Norman, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Ringwood, Thomas E., undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Roeder, Phillip W., undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Rosenberg, Stanford H., undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Ross, John P., undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Sagner, James S., undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Sellekaerts, Willy, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Shapiro, Martin M., undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Shine, Henry M., undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Sikula, Andrew F., undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Statler, Stuart M., undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Stinnett, Ronald, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Sutherland, Alan R., undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Uhlman, Thomas M., undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Upton, Charles, undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Wallace, Wanda A., undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Walker, Edward K., undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Walters, John R., undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Waters, Robert C., undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Meltzer, Jack, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Helms, robert S., undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Kidwell, David S., undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Kuhne, robert J., undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - West, Harry M., III, undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Lewicki, Roy J., undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Gross, Donald, undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Dunn, William, undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Concannon, George R., undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Ross, Bernard, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Cohen, Mark A., undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Himmelfard, Philip A., undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Schwendiman, John S., undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Hayden, Eric W., undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Tuggle, Francis Douglas, undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Wessell, Nils H., undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Wurtzel, Alan L., undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Asbaugh, Richard r., undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Bahramian, Bahram, undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Bernstein, Bernard, undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Boyd, Ronald L., undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Connell, Francis J., undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Risco, Gerald R., undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Cohen, Howard A., undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Maddocks, robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Cooke, Louis J., undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Roomkin, Myron J., undated (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Brennan, Bartley A., undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Edwards, Richard A., undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Reid, Irvin D., undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Faccone, Mary A., undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Gart, Alan, undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Golitz, Robert T., undated (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Dolich, Ira J., undated (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Lindenberg, Marc, undated (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Beaumont, Enid, undated (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Bremor, L. Paul, III, undated (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Haynes, Kingsley, undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Hriz, Andrew III, undated (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Pendergast, William R., undated (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Bisesi, Michael, undated (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Costello, Daniel E., undated (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Goldhar, Joel D., undated (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Helms, Robert B., undated (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Kooros, Syrous, undated (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Minter, robart L, undated (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Ross, Bernard H, undated (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Silver, Gerald, undated (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Tuckman, Howard P, undated (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Gradison, Heather J., undated (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Hopson, James k, undated (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Horner, Constance, undated (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Delbeco, Andre L., undated (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Henry, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Rotberg, Eugene H., undated (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Blood, Milton R., undated (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - McPherson, M. Peter, undated (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Reinhardt, Uwe E, undated (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Nalen Garig A., undated (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Kassichieh, Sol K., undated (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Keifaver, Thomas G., undated (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Kuhne, Robert J., undated (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Laessig, Walter B., undated (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Block, Michael K., undated (Box 1, Folder 128)
- Public Administration Department, 1970-1987; RG0013 Series 7; 6 Linear feet
  This series contains course feedback summaries, doctoral student surveys, alumni surveys, student handbooks, and annual reports. This material dates from 1970-87. Some of this material relates to the Museum Studies Program.
- Departmental files, 1985-1990; RG0013 Series 8; 10.5 Linear feet
  This series contains course syllabi, exams, course evaluations and annual reports. This material dates form 1985-90. Some of the people associated with these records include Suzanne Cory, Leo Moersen, Professor Singleton, Debra Sheldon, and Keith Smith. In addition, some of this material relates to Benjamin Franklin University.
  Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for 100 years from date of record creation.
- Finance Department, 1980-1996; RG0013 Series 9; 18 Linear feet
  This series contains minutes, committee records, annual reports, teaching load reports, grade sheets, registration, and budget records. This material dates from 1980-96. These records are for the Finance Department and include personnel records.
- Duques building, 2000; RG0013 Series 10; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains memos and drawings. This material is dated 2000. The material is about the proposed School of Business and Public Management building by Funger Hall called the Duques building.
- Departmental files, 1962-1988; RG0013 Series 11; 2 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series contains annual reports report of dean, minutes, five-year plan, student resumes, and papers. This material dates from 1962-88. The topic of accreditation is also part of this series.
  - Accreditation Task Force-Progress Report, 08/16/1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Leadership Laboratory, 06/08/1964-06/18/1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Application of the School of Government and Business Administration, Volume I, 06/1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Application of the School of Government and Business Administration, Volume II, 06/1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Enterprise Zones: A Capitol Venture, 12/1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Five-Year Planning Document School of Government and Business Administration, 01/1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Forecast of the Economic, Social, and Political Climate, 1975-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Forest Heights, Maryland Citizen Survey, 03/30/1974-03/31/1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - IBM Federal Systems Division Middle Management School, Airlie House, 09/25/1966-10/07/1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - IBM Federal Systems Division Middle Management School, Airlie House, 12/04/1966-12/16/1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - International Business Alumni Directory, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Part-time Faculty Data Sheets, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Reorganizing Federal Personnel Management, 1945-1960-Research Memorandum (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Research Paper-"The Role and Function of the United States Advisory Commission on Information", 05/1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Report of the Dean, 04/1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Resumes of students in doctoral programs of the School of Government and Business, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - School of G.B.I.A Faculty Meetings, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Survey of the More Advanced Executive Development Programs in the Federal Government, 05/31/1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Survey of the USSR Foreign Trade Structure, System, and Procedure, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Application for Continuing Accreditation, Faculty Data Sheets, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Application for Continuing Accreditation, Faculty Data Sheets/Affiliated Programs, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Issues of Concern to the Management Community, MGT 201, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Videotapes, 1988-1998; RG0013 Series 12; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)